https://www.osaonline.com/privacy-disclaimer/

Skip to content
Menu
Menu
Privacy Disclaimer
This Privacy Disclaimer explains how information about You is collected, used, and disclosed by Your access or use of this Site or otherwise as a result of Your interactions with Us. By visiting this Site directly or through another site, You accept the terms and conditions of this Policy. This Policy applies to this Site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any website not operated by Us to which this Site links or that links to this Site.
Information Collection
We collect information from you in several different ways on this Site.
Information We Collect Automatically
We may also automatically collect information about you when you access or use the Site or transact business with Us, including:
Log Information: We obtain information about your use of Our websites, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to this Site.
Device Information: We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access Our Services, such as the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information, and browsing behavior.
Location Information: We may collect information about the precise location of your device when you consent to the collection of this information. We may also collect information about your approximate location each time you access this Site.
Information Collected by Cookies and other Tracking Technologies: We may use cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies to collect information about you and your interaction with this Site, including information about your browsing behaviour, purchase behaviour, and other engagement with the Services. We use this information in one or more of the ways described in the “Use of Information” section below. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default, but you can usually change your browser settings to remove or reject cookies.
Information We Collect from Other Sources
We may also receive information about you from other sources and combine or link that with information We have about you. For example, We may collect demographic and change-of-address information from third party sources and information from third party social media platforms (such as Facebook) if you log into this Site using your social media account credentials or if you make certain content and information publicly available, such as photos, videos, and profile information.
Information Use and Disclosure
Internal Use
We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally your personal information to improve this Site’s content and layout, to improve outreach and for Our own marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to this Site.
Communications with You
We will use your personal information to communicate with you about this Site and your orders and deliveries. Also, We may send you a confirmation email when you register with Us. We may send you a service-related announcement on the rare occasions when it is necessary (for example, if we must temporarily suspend our service for maintenance.) Also, you may submit your email address for reasons such as to register for a contest or sweepstakes or to sign up for email newsletters and special offers. If you submit your email address, We use it to deliver the information to you. We always permit you to unsubscribe or opt out of future emails.
External Use
Except as otherwise set forth below, We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone.
We may disclose information to third parties that perform specific functions on Our behalf.  However, We will only disclose the information that is necessary for them to perform their service.
While We will not sell (or trade or rent) personally identifiable information to other companies as part of Our regular course of business. However, it’s possible that We might acquire or merge with or be acquired by another company or that We might dispose of some or all of Our assets. If that happens, your personal information may be disclosed to another company, but that disclosure will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect.
We may share non-personal information (such as the number of daily visitors to a particular web page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date) with third parties such as advertising partners. This information does not directly personally identify you or any user.
Data Security
We take reasonable measures, including administrative, technical, and physical safeguards, to protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.
Opt Out/Corrections
Upon your request, We will (a) correct or update your personal information; (b) stop sending emails to your email address; and/or (c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. You can make these requests by emailing us:  general@osaonline.com
Please do not email sensitive information.
Offline Collection Use and Disclosure
We also may collect information offline. We will treat any information collected offline in a manner that is consistent with this Policy.  One example involves someone calling Us to place an order or to ask questions. When someone calls, We will ask only for the personal information We need in order to place the order or to answer the question. When We need to store information (such as order information), We will enter it into our database.
Updates to this Policy
If We change or update this Privacy Policy, We will post changes and updates on the Site so that you will always be aware of what information We collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Policy, please contact us via out contact us page
Search
Pages
About Me
Speak To Us
Gamerfied Workshops
Advertise With Us
Gamer FAQ
Tips To Offer?
Factual Source- Your Guide To Gaming Info
Privacy Disclaimer
Sitemap
Free Online Games
That Crazy Owner
Hey! I'm Jeri Wright. I have been a gamer since I fell in love with two plumbers called the Super Mario Brothers. Don't hesitate to browse around my site and leave your comments on any of the pages. May the force be with you!
Latest E3 2014
About Me
Advertise With Us
Factual Source- Your Guide To Gaming Info
Gamer FAQ
Gamerfied Workshops
Privacy Disclaimer
Speak To Us
Tips To Offer?
Sitemap
